gameshadow.com 2006-10-25

# GameShadow.com – Get the latest patch, demo or trailer for your games

**Privacy Policy  
**GameShadow is a Service and Software Product. When we refer to "we" or "our" we are referring to GameShadow Limited.  When we refer in this Privacy Policy to "our website" we are referring to the website at http://www.gameshadow.com.

GameShadow Limited is registered in England number 5502662 and its registered address is 37 MAIN STREET,OVER NORTON, OXFORDSHIRE, OX7 5PR, UNITED KINGDOM. 

**Why do we have a Privacy Policy?**  
GameShadow Limited is registered under the data protection laws in the United Kingdom and takes all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal information.  When we refer to "personal information" in this Privacy Policy, we mean information which identifies, or is capable of identifying, you as an individual. 

However, in addition to our legal obligations, we have developed this Privacy Policy because we want you to feel confident about the privacy and security of the personal information you disclose to us when you register for our services or, as a visitor, enter into any of our competitions or promotions.  If you only browse our website we do not collect any personal information from you but we may gather anonymous information (using cookies) to help make your visit to our website more satisfying.  Please see "Other information we collect" for more information on how we do this. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.  If you are visiting our website or using our services, you indicate your agreement to our use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy by continuing to use our website.  If you want to register for or order one of our services, you will also be asked to accept this Privacy Policy during registration. 

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**  
This Privacy Policy only applies to our website and services.  It does not apply to any third party or other GameShadow Limited sites whichGameShadow Limited may host or which you may access from our website or any other GameShadow Limited or third party services. If you choose to disclose your personal information directly to other companies, your personal information will be dealt with according to those companies' privacy practices. 

As our website is an evolving, developing website, some parts of our website have their own privacy policies, in which case those policies will apply when you visit those areas or use the services offered there. 

**When do we collect personal information from you?**  
If you register to become a subscriber or a customer of GameShadow, we may ask you for information such as your name, address, contact telephone numbers, email address, credit card details and other (optional) information.  We may also ask you for personal information if you subscribe to our newsletter and if you enter one of the competitions or promotions on our website. 

Once in a while we may receive personal information about you from third parties.  Except in the cases where we are merely processing such information on their behalf, such third parties should have requested your consent for us to use this information. 

**What do we use your personal information for?**  
If you are a registered customer we may use your personal information to: 

| 

Communicate with you about your access to or use of our service   
  
---|---  
| 

Check that you are a registered customer if you call the GameShadow Limited offices, or use the email support facility.  Should you make contact by telephone, for security reasons we will ask you some of the information you gave us when you registered and check this against our records.   
  
| 

Collect payment from you   
  
| 

Let you know (by post, telephone or e-mail) about any changes to our services or our website   
  
| 

Contact you to ask whether you would like to join in one of our research groups to help us improve our service to you but not by disclosing your details to third parties   
  
| 

Improve our understanding of the type of customers we are attracting to our services and how they use our services   
  
| 

Subject to your agreement, provide you with information about GameShadow Limited and/or third party products and services   
  
| 

Manage our network.   
  
If you enter one of our competitions or promotions, we use the personal information you provide to manage the competition or promotion you have entered. 

We may sometimes ask other companies to provide any of the above services on our behalf. If we do this, we share your personal information with them for this purpose.  Please see "Do we share your personal information with anyone else?" for more information on this. 

**What other information do we collect?**  
We have information about your use of our GameShadow services (such as the amount of time you are connected to the service). We mainly use this information to manage our network. However, we may also use this information for marketing GameShadow Limited's services.  We do not disclose this information to anyone other than to our agents who process it on our behalf. Your decision on whether you want to receive details of other GameShadow Limited products and services made when you register for or order a service also applies to this information. Consequently, if you do not wish us to use this information for marketing purposes but during registration elected to receive details on other GameShadow Limited products and services, you will need to write to [marketing@gameshadow.com ](mailto:marketing@gameshadow.com) and request that you opt-out from us using your information for marketing purposes. 

When you use the GameShadow service, all the deductive logic to determine the versions of your games is conducted locally on your PC. We do not transfer or transmit any game related information held on your computer or network to the GameShadow servers. 

As with most (if not all) website operators, we also collect anonymous information from visitors to our website and registered customers to help us improve our website and the services we make available. This anonymous information tells us, for instance, how many visitors there were to our website, when they visited, for how long and which areas of our website they went visited. This information helps us to assess which parts of our website are popular or need improving. We may share this aggregate data with our advertisers and other companies which offer their goods or services on our website so that they can see how effective our website is as a sales channel for their products. Remember though that they, and we, cannot see which individuals this data relates to - it only shows the usage patterns of a particular PC. 

We **do not** use this anonymous information to: 

| 

identify individuals visiting our website   
  
---|---  
| 

analyse your visits to any other websites (except that we do track you if you go to websites carrying our banner, but we do not identify personal details while we do this)   
  
| 

track any internet searches which you may make while on our website.   
  
**How do we collect anonymous information?**  
We use "cookies" on our Forums to collect anonymous information from visitors to our website and registered customers. A "cookie" is a text file which is allocated by our server to your PC when you visit our website. The text file contains a random number which, unless the cookie is deleted, allows us to identify your PC if you visit our website again. 

Our servers use two different types of cookies.  The first type is known as a "session-based" cookie and is allocated to your PC only for the duration of your visit to our website. It helps you to move around the website faster and, if you are a registered customer or subscriber, it allows us to give you information relevant to GameShadow. This cookie automatically expires when you close down your browser. 

Other companies which advertise or offer their products or services on our website may also allocate cookies to your PC. The types of cookies they use and how they use the information generated by them will be governed by those companies' privacy policies, not ours. 

All types of cookies can be removed from your PC. However, if you do this there is likely to be a deterioration of your experience of our website (e.g.: you may end up being shown endless numbers of pop up boxes containing the same advertisements or not being able to see a personalised page).  Your browser lets you choose whether to accept, not to accept, or to be warned before accepting cookies.  These settings can be found in the advanced preferences -   
**In Internet Explorer select:** Tools menu / Internet options / Security / Custom Level   
**In Netscape 4.x select:** Edit menu / Preferences / Advanced 

**Do we share your personal information with anyone else?**  
We sometimes have to share your personal information with other companies which we use to provide some of our own services. For example, we use specialist companies to conduct market research on our behalf to see how we can improve the services we offer to our customers. We would need to give those companies your personal information so that they can contact you to see if you'd like to participate in our market research. However, those companies can only process this information according to the instructions we give them. 

We also share your personal information with other parts of GameShadow Limited or other companies so that they (or we, on their behalf) can contact you with details of other products or services you may be interested in.  We will only do this if you have agreed to receive this information.  During your registration as a GameShadow customer, or if you enter a promotion or competition on our website, you can decide whether you would like this information. 

If you agree to receive information about other companies' products and services, we will only share your personal information with those companies if they agree to use your personal information only for that purpose. 

If you are a subscriber to our newsletter and no longer wish to receive the newsletter please go to: [www.gameshadow.com ](http://www.gameshadow.com/) and use the ‘My Account' area once you have logged in.  You may unsubscribe by unticking the newsletter check-box. 

To the extent required by law, we will disclose your personal information to law enforcement and other government agencies. You should also be aware that if you are a registered customer and we find that you are using our services for illegal purposes, we may investigate how you are doing so and prohibit you from using the service.  We may ultimately notify the police. If we receive a Court Order requesting us to reveal your identity to someone complaining that you have used our service abusively, we will do so. 

If there is a change (or prospective change) in the ownership of GameShadow Limited or any of its assets, we may have to disclose personal information to the new (or prospective) owner. 

**How can I change the personal information GameShadow Limited holds about me?**  
If you are a registered customer, you have direct control over the personal information GameShadow Limited holds about you.  If you need to make any changes to the personal details GameShadow Limited holds about you, please send details of the changes to [contact@gameshadow.com ](mailto:contact@gameshadow.com)

You may always log into the ‘My Account' area of the www.gameshadow.com website and change any of your details online, following the instructions laid out in that part of the website. 

**How can I find out what personal information GameShadow Limited holds about me?**  
If you want to know what personal information GameShadow Limited holds about you, you can obtain it, as long as you are a GameShadow customer.  Please write to the following address, stating that you are a GameShadow customer or subscriber and enclose a cheque for the administration fee of £10 made payable to “GameShadow Limited” under the terms of the Data Protection Act: 

GameShadow Limited  
37 Main Street   
Over Norton   
Oxfordshire  
OX7 5PR, UK 

If the information we hold about you is inaccurate, please let us know and we will make the necessary amendments and confirm that these have been made. 

**How do we protect your personal information?**  
We use a secure server to store the information you give us when you register (including your credit card details and your password).  Any personal data you send us is securely encrypted. 

Over and above what GameShadow Limited does to safeguard your privacy and security, there are a number of things you can do to protect yourself from Internet fraud: 

| 

Choose a password you can remember but others will not guess, and, if you do write it down, keep it somewhere safe and secure.   
  
---|---  
| 

When you have finished your session on our website, make sure you prevent your details being seen by anyone that you do not wish to see them. So, if you have registered and logged in, remember to log off.  
Clear any cache so there is no record of any transactions left on screen - both Netscape and Internet Explorer let you do this. We also recommend you then close your browser so any history of the session is cleared.   
  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do change this Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page and may place notices on other pages of our website, so that you will be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to such changes. If you are a registered customer or a subscriber, we will notify you of the changed policy.
